

CONTACT ME

+971 56445 1682

sharjah,UAE

abhiramps776@gmail.com

https://abhiramps.vercel.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ abhiram-p-s-947b92157/

https://github.com/abhiramps

SKILLS SUMMARY

ReactJS.NextJs

•••• Tailwindcss,chakraUI

•••• Bootstrap5,materialUI

•••• HTML5,CSS3,SCSS

•••• Redux

•••• REST, Graph QI API

•••• Prisma ORM

•••• GIT,Github

Responsive,UI/UX

•••• AWS amplify,Cognito

Redux.ExpressJs

●●●● DynamoDb,MongoDB,PlanetScale

●●●● Vercel,Heroku,Netlify



ABHIRAM PS

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

As a Fullstack stack developer, I have nearly a year of experience and knowledge of web development technologies,including, NextJs, Aws Amplify, Tailwindcss, DynamoDb.

I seek the opportunity to prove my skills in a demanding environment and to utilize my knowledge and intelligence in order to enhance the success of the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Shaikhtech, UAE | Dec 2021 - Present

- Designed and coded websites, from layout to function, according to client specifications.
- Created Graphql's API for NextJs(Frontend) using AWS amplify
- Used Graphql's subscriptions for displaying Real-time Data from DynamoDb
- Research and provide value add to the product.

JUNIOR MERN STACK DEVELOPER

Enfin technologies, INDIA | Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

- Assisted the development of web applications.
- Report daily status to senior developers.
- Builds and shapes a visitor's experience on the site.
- Creates page layouts, site style, and page features

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER TRAINEE

Luminar technolab, INDIA | 2020 nov -2021 april

- Created Web applications using ReactJs, Angular2+ and backend with ExpressJs.Collaborated with other designers
- Report daily status to senior developers.

AWARDS RECEIVED

- NACTET Certification MEA(R)N STACK
 DEVELOPMENT (Nov 2020 Apr 2021)
- Web development ICT Academy
 (July 2017 5 days)

PERSONAL DETAILS

AGE : 23 years

NATIONALITY : Indian

MARITAL STATUS : Single

VISA STATUS : Visit Visa valid

till march 29

PROJECTS

FLEET MANAGEMENT

Client: WORLD STAR | Dec 2021 - Present

- A Fuel delivery system for managing and processing Real-time data of customers and displaying it on the front end.
- Built using AWS amplify for managing backend, Graphql for API, Amazon Cognito User Pools for managing authentication.
- Technologies used: NextJs, ChakraUI, AWS Amplify, Graphql, cogito,react-hook-from,DynamoDb

EHR SHARING USING BLOCKCHAIN

(CAMPUS PROJECT) | Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

- Focused on storing and processing patient health record data. Built using smart contracts and deployed using testnets.IPFS for file handling.
- Technologies used: Solidity, Web3.js, Ganache, Metamask, Reactjs

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

APJ ABDUL KALAM TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY, INDIA

BE/B.TECH in Computer science and Engineering | Aug 2016 - Oct 2020